<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Asura Linux Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.asuralinux.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Asura Linux Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.asuralinux.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Linux Boot Sequence</title>
      <link>https://blog.asuralinux.org/2023/10/understanding-the-linux-boot-sequence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.asuralinux.org/2023/10/understanding-the-linux-boot-sequence/</guid>
      <description>In my previous post on the Asura Linux blog, I introduced Asura Linux as an Open Source project to experiment with different ways of building and running modern general-purpose Linux systems—and to share what we learn along the way. I explained why the Asura Linux Project exists and what I was thinking about the immediate future. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, please have a look.
In my excitement about introducing the project, I promised to publish the second blog post about the Linux boot process shortly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://blog.asuralinux.org/2023/10/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.asuralinux.org/2023/10/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! Welcome to the Asura Linux Project. This is the first of hopefully many posts in the fresh new Asura Linux blog. It almost smells like fresh paint and a just-mowed lawn here.
I recently started Asura Linux as a new Open Source project to explore the possibilities of building modern Linux systems with emerging foundational userspace technologies and concepts—ultimately guided by user experience. In simpler words, I want to experiment with different ways of building and running Linux systems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
